plazahotelcasino.com 2006-12-06

# Downtown Las Vegas Hotel & Casino - plazahotelcasino.com

[Home](http://www.plazahotelcasino.com/) > Privacy Policy 

PLAZA HOTEL & CASINO ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY

**OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**  
Your privacy is extremely important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**APPLICATION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
This Privacy Policy applies to all Web sites including, but not limited to, the Web sites for: (1) Plaza Hotel & Casino at www.plazahotelcasino.com; (2) Vegas Club Hotel & Casino at www.vegasclubcasino.net; (3) Western Hotel & Casino at www.westernhotelcasino.com; and (4) Gold Spike Hotel & Casino at www.goldspikehotelcasino.com. Our Web sites may be accessed through domain names other than the domain names listed above. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by us by means other than through our Web sites.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU**  
**General Information**  
When you visit our Web sites, we track certain information that is non-personally identifiable. Data is collected in aggregate and anonymously, which may include the type of Internet browser you use, the type of computer operating system you have, the pages you visit on our Web sites, and how you arrived at our Web sites.

**Personally Identifiable Information**  
The personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide is used in order to conduct particular transactions on our Web sites including room reservations. The information we collect may include name, address, birth date, telephone number, email address and, credit card information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small file that contains information sent by a Web site that is saved on your hard drive by your computer's browser. Cookies store information that a Web site may need to personalize your experience and to gather Web site statistical data, such as which pages you visit, what material you download, your Internet provider's domain name and country, and the addresses of Web sites you visit immediately before and after visiting a particular Web site.

We use cookies to collect and store your preferences for viewing our Web sites, such as whether you disable multi-media capabilities so that you will not have to do so on follow up visits. In addition, we use cookies to provide a unique identifier to your computer so that we can generate statistics regarding usage of our Web sites, such as the percentage of repeat visitors and other general statistics. The unique identifiers are not matched with any personally identifiable information. In addition, when you book a reservation online to stay at one of our properties, the reservation or confirmation number may be stored in a cookie on your computer. Cookies used by us do NOT store any personally identifiable information about you.

To browse the Internet and our Web sites without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies, or to notify you when each cookie is offered so that you can either accept or reject each cookie. You may not be able to conduct some transactions or use some services on our Web sites if you do decide to disable your browser from accepting cookies.

**HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
We collect personally identifiable information about you in order to provide you with a personalized web experience. We use your contact data to send you information about our properties and current promotions, and to contact you when necessary. We use your financial data for billing of products and services. Your demographic data is used to customize your site experience and to deliver specific content that may be of interest to you.

**SHARING OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
We will not sell, trade, or disclose to third parties any personally identifiable information obtained through our Web sites without your consent unless required to do so by law. We may disclose personally identifiable information in order to: (1) enforce our Web site Agreement; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of PlayLV Gaming Corporation; (3) comply with a court order or other legal process or legal requirements of any governmental authorities, including but not limited to, authorities which regulate gaming activities; or (4) in the sole discretion of PlayLV Gaming Corporation, in exceptional circumstances, such as a national emergency, security concern, or other situation in which we deem such disclosure is prudent.

**CHOICE REGARDING PROVIDING INFORMATION**  
General information is collected whenever you browse our Web sites. Our Web sites do not provide any means for opting out of providing general information when you browse our Web sites. However, privacy software that prevents the disclosure of general information is commercially available.

You can browse our Web sites without providing any personally identifiable information. However, providing personally identifiable information is required to use some of the services offered through our Web sites, including, but not limited to, making reservations, signing up for promotions, or participating in sweepstakes.

You can opt out of receiving certain communications and offers. Opt out options will be indicated when they are available.

**SECURITY**  
General information and personally identifiable information collected by our Web sites is stored on secure servers. The secure servers are protected by firewalls and other standard security procedures. The secure servers are not generally accessible by unauthorized third parties, but could become accessible in the event of a security breach. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us.

Once we receive your information, we take appropriate steps that we believe are reasonable to protect the security of your data on our system, both internally and from outsiders, and to ensure the integrity of the data we collect. We use a combination of technological and policy methods to protect this data. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. Please be aware that we will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email. 

**AGE RESTRICTIONS AND THE CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT**  
Pursuant to law, persons under the age of twenty-one (21) are not permitted to gamble in casinos and are not permitted to loiter in the gaming areas of any of our properties. Similarly, our Web sites are general audience sites intended for persons 21 years of age or older. Persons younger than 21 years of age are not allowed to use our Web sites, accept offers, or win contest, and we do not knowingly collect information from such persons. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not knowingly collect or accept personally identifiable information from a child under the age of thirteen (13). 

**HOW YOU MAY CHANGE, CORRECT YOUR REGISTRATION INFORMATION**  
If you want to change, correct, update, or delete your registration information, please contact us via email at privacy@playlv.com, call us at (702) 876-1001, or send your request to PlayLV Gaming Corporation, Attn: Registration Information Correction, 501 S. Rancho, Suite B-10, Las Vegas, NV 89106, and the necessary revisions will be made. This provision applies only to registration information collected via the Web sites. 

**CHANGES**  
We reserve the right to modify or change this Privacy Policy at any time, simply by posting such changes on the Web site. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@playlv.com](mailto:privacy@playlv.com).
